International Fur and Leather Workers Union Records 5676
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Miscellaneous, 1944 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  includes strike card; attendance list; handwritten notes; a report on the Leather Industry; Canada, 1944, 28 p.
- Photos - Greek Fur Workers, Local 70. (Box 32, Folder 10)